Guide to the Yale Classes Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Pictures of Yale Classes, 1806-1971; Series I
  - Classes of 1927 & 1927s 30th Reunion, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 591)
  - Class of 1927s
    - Small group (Box 51, Folder 591)
    - 10th Reunion, 1937 (Box 51, Folder 592)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 51, Folder 592)
  - Class of 1928
    - 30th Reunion, 1958 (Box 51, Folder 593)
    - 40th Reunion, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 593)
    - 55th Reunion, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 593a)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 51, Folder 594)
  - Classes of 1928 & 1928s 40th Reunion, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 595)
  - Class of 1928s: Reunion, undated (Box 51, Folder 596)
  - Class of 1929
    - Triennial Reunion, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 597)
    - Sexennial Reunion, 1935 (Box 52, Folder 597)
    - Decennial Reunion, 1939 (Box 52, Folder 597)
    - 20th Reunion, 1949 (Box 52, Folder 598)
    - 25th Reunion, 1954 (Box 52, Folder 598)
      Scope and Contents
      Color slides taken by Andrew Davis Carroll.
    - 40th Reunion, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 598)
  - Class of 1929s: Small group (Box 52, Folder 599)
  - Class of 1930
    - Reunion, 1959 (Box 52, Folder 600)
    - 30th Reunion, 1960 (Box 52, Folder 600)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 52, Folder 600)
    - Later Individual portraits (Box 52, Folder 600)
    - Assorted later snapshots (Box 52, Folder 601)
  - Class of 1930s: Later snapshots (Box 52, Folder 602)
  - Class of 1931: Reunions (Box 52, Folder 602a)
  - Class of 1931s: Reunion, Undated (Box 52, Folder 603)
  - Class of 1932
    - 10th Reunion, 1942 (Box 52, Folder 604)
    - 20th Reunion, 1952 (Box 52, Folder 604)
    - 35th Reunion, 1952 (Box 52, Folder 604)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 52, Folder 605)
  - Class of 1933
    - 25th reunion, 1958 (Box 52, Folder 606)
    - 35th reunion, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 606)
  - Class of 1934
    - Small group, 1931 (Box 52, Folder 607)
    - Snapshot (Box 52, Folder 607)
    - 35th Reunion, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 607)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 52, Folder 607)
  - Class of 1934s: Snapshots Sheffield Triennial Committee (Box 52, Folder 608)
  - Class of 1935
    - Triennial Reunion, 1938 (Box 52, Folder 609)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 52, Folder 609)
  - Class of 1935s
    - Class picture (Box 52, Folder 610)
  - Class of 1936
    - Class picture (Box 52, Folder 611)
    - Prom party (Box 52, Folder 611)
    - 35th Reunion, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 611)
    - Photographs for the reunion book Fifty Years Out, Circa 1986 (Box 52, Folder 611a-611b)
  - Class of 1936s
    - Small group (Box 52, Folder 612)
    - Triennial Reunion, 1939 (Box 52, Folder 612)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 52, Folder 612)
  - Class of 1937
    - Graduation snapshot (Box 52, Folder 613)
    - 30th Reunion, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 613)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 52, Folder 613)
  - Class of 1937s: Class picture (Box 52, Folder 614)
  - Class of 1938
    - Berkeley College Students (Box 52, Folder 615)
    - Seniors at Pierson College (Box 52, Folder 615)
    - Commencement photographs (Box 52, Folder 616)
    - 20th Reunion, 1958 (Box 52, Folder 617)
    - 30th Reunion, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 617)
  - Class of 1938: Reunions, Undated (Box 52, Folder 618)
  - Class of 1939
    - Trumbull College Students (Box 52, Folder 619)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 52, Folder 619)
  - Class of 1940
    - Dinner, 1941 (Box 52, Folder 620)
    - Individual portraits (Box 52, Folder 620)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 52, Folder 620A)
  - Classes of 1940 & 1940s
    - Individual portraits
      - A - Coo (Box 53, Folder 621)
      - Cor - Go (Box 53, Folder 622)
      - Ket - Ne (Box 53, Folder 624)
      - Ni - Se (Box 53, Folder 625)
      - Sh - Ti (Box 53, Folder 626)
      - To - Y (Box 53, Folder 627)
  - Class of 1940s: Individual portraits (Box 53, Folder 628)
  - Class of 1942
    - Class Council (Box 54, Folder 629)
    - Class Day (Box 54, Folder 629)
    - Small groups (Box 54, Folder 629)
    - Branford College Group (Box 54, Folder 630)
    - 25th Reunion, 1967 (Box 54, Folder 630)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 54, Folder 630)
    - Reunion-- Yale Club of New York, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 631)
  - Class of 1943
    - Sexennial Reunion, 1949 (Box 54, Folder 632)
    - 25th Reunion, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 632)
  - Class of 1944
    - Branford College Group (Box 54, Folder 633)
    - Pierson College Group (Box 54, Folder 633)
    - 25th Reunion, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 633)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 54, Folder 634)
  - Class of 1945: Reunion, Undated (Box 54, Folder 635)
  - Class of 1946
    - Triennial Reunion, 1949 (Box 54, Folder 636)
    - Sexennial Reunion, 1952 (Box 54, Folder 636)
    - 25th Reunion, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 636)
  - Class of 1947
    - Triennial, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 637)
    - 20th Reunion, 1967 (Box 54, Folder 637)
    - 55th Reunion, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 637)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 54, Folder 637)
    - Class of 1947N: Branford College group (Box 54, Folder 638)
  - Class of 1948
    - 10th Reunion, 1958 (Box 54, Folder 639)
    - 20th Reunion, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 639)
  - Class of 1949: 20th Reunion, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 640)
  - Class of 1951: 20th Reunion, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 641)
  - Class of 1952: 15th Reunion, 1967 (Box 54, Folder 642)
  - Class of 1953: 15th Reunion, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 643)
  - Class of 1956: 15th Reunion, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 644)
  - Class of 1957: Branford College group 10th Reunion, 1967 (Box 54, Folder 645)
  - Class of 1958: 10th Reunion, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 646)
  - Class of 1961: 10th Reunion, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 647)
  - Class of 1962
    - Various College Class groups (Box 54, Folder 648)
    - 5th Reunion, 1967 (Box 54, Folder 648)
  - Class of 1963
    - 5th Reunion, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 649)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 54, Folder 649)
  - Class of 1964: 5th Reunion, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 650)
  - Class of 1966: 5th Reunion, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 651)
  - Class Reunion Activities
    - 1908 (Box 54, Folder 652)
    - [1910?] (Box 54, Folder 652)
    - [1937?] (Box 54, Folder 652)
    - [1939?] (Box 54, Folder 653)
    - 1940 (Box 54, Folder 653)
    - 1941 (Box 54, Folder 653)
    - 1942 (Box 54, Folder 654)
    - 1952 (Box 54, Folder 654)
    - 1967 (Box 54, Folder 654)
    - 1968 (Box 54, Folder 655)
    - 1969 (Box 54, Folder 655)
    - 1969 (Box 55, Folder 656)
    - 1971 (Box 55, Folder 657)
  - Unidentified Class Reunions
    - [Circa 1900?] (Box 55, Folder 658)
    - Pre-1920 (Box 55, Folder 658)
    - [1920-1950?] (Box 55, Folder 659)
  - Unidentified
    - [Pre-1900?] (Box 55, Folder 660)
    - [Circa 1900?] (Box 55, Folder 661-662)
  - Unidentified
    - Chemistry group 192-?, [1920-1950] (Box 55, Folder 663)
- Oversize pictures of Yale Classes, 1852-1970; Series II
  - 1852S (Box 56A, Folder 1)
  - 1856 (Box 56A, Folder 2)
  - 1858 (Box 56A, Folder 3)
  - 1860 (Box 56A, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1860 Reunion - Photographs of 40th and 50th Reunion, 1900, 1910 (Box 56A, Folder 5)
  - 1863 (Box 56A, Folder 6)
  - Skeleton Club, 1863 (Box 56A, Folder 7)
  - 1867 (Box 56A, Folder 8)
  - 1868 (Box 56A, Folder 9)
  - 1870 (Box 56A, Folder 10)
  - 1871 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - 1871 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - 1874 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - 1875 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - 1877 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - 1879 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - School of Fine Arts, 1880 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - 1887 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - 1889 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Group photo - Class of 1889 30th Reunion, Circa 1929 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - 1889 Senior Picture (with lists of students) (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - 1893 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - 1894 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - 1895 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - 1895S (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - 1896 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Reunion, Undated (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Cartoons for Decennial Record (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - 1897 (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - 1897S (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - 1898 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - 1898S (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - Unidentified, 1800s (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - 1900S (Box 59, Folder 34)
  - 1901 (Box 59, Folder 35)
  - Sheffield, 1901S (Box 59, Folder 36)
  - 1902S (Box 59, Folder 37)
  - Yale College Class of 1903 (Box 59, Folder 38)
  - Drawing Used in Quarter Century Records (Box 59, Folder 39)
  - 1904 (Box 59, Folder 40)
  - [1904S?] (Box 59, Folder 41)
  - 1905 (Box 59, Folder 42)
  - 1906S (Box 59, Folder 43)
  - 1907 (Box 59, Folder 44)
  - 1907S (Box 60, Folder 45)
  - 1908 (Box 60, Folder 46)
  - 1908S (Box 60, Folder 47)
  - Freshman Class (?) (Box 60, Folder 48)
  - 1909 (Box 60, Folder 49)
  - 1909S (Box 60, Folder 50)
  - 1910S (Box 60, Folder 51)
  - Freshman Picture?, 1910 (Box 60, Folder 52)
  - Class and Reunions (Box 60, Folder 53)
  - Reunion Photos, 1910 (Box 61, Folder 54 - 55)
  - Five photos, 1911 (Box 61, Folder 56)
  - Class Day and Class Costume group (2) photos, 1911 (Box 61, Folder 57)
  - 1911 (Box 61, Folder 58)
  - 1912 (Box 61, Folder 59)
  - Class of 1912 and 40th Reunion, 1912, 1952 (Box 62, Folder 60)
  - Class of 1912 45th Reunion, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 61)
  - 1912S (Box 62, Folder 62)
  - Class of 1913 Reunion, Circa 1923 (Box 62, Folder 62A)
  - 1913S (Box 62, Folder 63)
  - 1914 (Box 62, Folder 63A)
  - 1914S (Box 62, Folder 64)
  - School of Religion at Divinity, 1915 (Box 62, Folder 65)
  - 1915S (Box 62, Folder 66)
  - 6th Reunion, 10th Reunion, 15th Reunion, 20th Reunion, 1921, 1925, 1930, 1935 (Box 62, Folder 67)
  - 25th Reunion, 30th Reunion, 35th Reunion, 65th Reunion, 1940, 1947, 1950, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 68)
    General
    See: Folio
  - Vanderbilt Seniors, Fall 1914 (Box 62, Folder 69)
  - 1916 (Box 62, Folder 70)
  - 1916S (Box 62, Folder 71)
  - (Fragments)-broken picture of 1916 (Box 63, Folder 72)
  - 1917S (Box 63, Folder 73)
  - 1918S (Box 63, Folder 74)
  - 1919 (Box 63, Folder 75)
  - Class of 1919 1st Reunion Photographs, 1920 (Box 63, Folder 76)
  - Class of 1919 50th Reunion Photographs, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 77)
  - Class of 1919 55th Reunion Photographs, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 78)
  - 1919S (Box 63, Folder 79)
  - 1920S (Box 63, Folder 80)
  - Class of 1920 Yale Club Annual Dinner, 1952 (Box 63, Folder 81)
  - 1921 Medical, 1921S, 1922S (Box 63, Folder 82)
  - 1924, 1924S Reunion (Box 63, Folder 83)
  - Class of 1925 Reunion, Undated (Box 63, Folder 84)
  - 1926 (Box 63, Folder 84)
  - 1926S (Box 63, Folder 85)
  - 1927, 1927S (Box 63, Folder 86)
  - Class of 1928 40th Reunion, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 87)
  - 1928S (Box 63, Folder 87)
  - 1930 (Box 63, Folder 88)
  - 1930S (Box 63, Folder 89)
  - 1931, 1931S (Box 64, Folder 90)
  - 1932S (Box 64, Folder 91)
  - 1933S (Box 64, Folder 92)
  - 1934S (Box 64, Folder 93)
  - 1935 (Box 64, Folder 94)
  - Drawings used in Senior Class Book, 1935 (Box 64, Folder 95)
  - 1935S (Box 64, Folder 96)
  - Trumbull College Students, 1936-1937, undated (Box 64, Folder 97)
  - Drawings used in Senior Class Book, 1937 (Box 64, Folder 98)
  - 1939S (Box 64, Folder 99)
  - Class of 1940 20th reunion, 1960 (Box 64, Folder 99A)
  - Class of 1940 25th reunion, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 99A)
  - 1944S (Box 64, Folder 100)
  - 1945W (Box 64, Folder 101)
  - 1945S (Box 64, Folder 102)
  - Class of 1962 5th and 15th reunion, 1967, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 102a)
  - Berkeley College, 1961, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 103)
  - Berkeley College, 1963, 1964 (Box 65, Folder 104)
  - Berkeley College, 1965, 1968 (Box 65, Folder 105)
  - Berkeley College, 1969, 1970 (Box 65, Folder 106)
  - Branford College Class of 1962 (Box 65, Folder 106a)
  - Unidentified, 1900s (Box 65, Folder 107)
- Folio pictures of Yale Classes, 1856-1960; Series III
  - Classes of 1856-1868 (Folder DR3F12)
  - Classes of 1870-1872 (Folder DR3F13)
  - Class of 1873 (Folder DR3F14)
  - Class of 1876 (Folder DR4F15)
  - Class of 1878 (Folder DR4F16)
  - Classes of 1879-1884 (Folder DR5F18)
  - Classes of 1887-1889 (Folder DR5F19)
  - Classes of 1890-1895 (Folder DR5F20)
  - Class of 1894
    - 20th reunion, 1914 (Folder DR32F98)
    - 25th reunion, 1919 (Folder DR5F20)
  - Classes of 1896-1899, 1915 (Folder DR6F21)
  - Class of 1897, 25th reunion, 1922 (Folder DR32F98)
  - Classes of 1900-1901 (Folder DR6F22)
  - Classes of 1902-1904 (Folder DR7F23)
  - Class of 1904, Circa 1904 (Folder DR32F98A)
  - Class of 1905 (Folder DR7F24)
  - Classes of 1906-1907 (Folder DR8F25)
  - Classes of 1908-1909 (Folder DR8F26)
  - Class of 1910, 1910S (Folder DR9F27)
  - Class of 1910, 20th reunion, 1930 (Folder DR32F98)
  - Class of 1911 (graduation) (Folder DR32F98)
  - Class of 1911s, Class Day (Folder DR120)
  - Class of 1911S, Circa 1911 (Folder DR32F98A)
  - Class of 1912 (class day) (Folder DR32F98)
    - Undated (Folder DR9F28)
  - Class of 1912s (Folder DR9F28)
  - Class of 1913 (Folder DR10F29)
  - Class of 1913 (class day) (Folder DR32F98)
  - Class of 1914 (Folder DR10F29)
  - Class of 1915 (Folder DR32F98)
  - Class of 1915 (Folder DR10F30)
  - Class of 1915 (Folder DR11F31)
  - Class of 1915, 1911-1947 (Folder DR32F98A)
  - Classes of 1916-1919 (Folder DR11F32)
  - Classes 1920-1925 (Folder DR12F33)
  - Class of 1923, Circa 1923 (Folder DR32F98A)
  - Classes 1926-1930 (Folder DR12F34)
  - Class of 1928, Circa 1928 (Folder DR32F98A)
  - Class of 1929 (Folder DR32F98)
  - Classes 1931-1960 (Folder DR12F35)
  - Class of 1934, Circa 1934 (Folder DR32F98A)
  - Class of 1935, 1936, 1938, 1960 (Folder DR32F98)
  - Class of 1936, Circa 1936 (Folder DR32F98A)
  - Unidentified class groups (Folder DR12F36)
  - Unidentified class groups (Folder DR32F98)
- Sheffield Scientific School Class of 1909, 1908-1909; Accession 2017-A-059
  - Civil Engineering graduating class of 1909, Robert A. Riley identified, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified group of Sheffield students, with Robert Annan Riley identified, Circa 1909 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Sheffield Scientific School Class of 1917, Undated; Accession 2018-A-0047
  - Photographs of students from the Sheffield Scientific School Class of 1917, Donald C. Root identified., Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)